healthwarehouse.com 2016-08-12

# Privacy - HealthWarehouse.com

#### Processing time for _OTC products_ remains 1-3 business days. Currently we're experiencing a surge in _prescription medication_ order volume and are temporarily adding 2-4 extra days to normal prescription processing times. As always, we will ship your order as quickly as possible.

**HealthWarehouse.com is a[licensed US pharmacy](http://vipps.nabp.net/verify.asp). We offer an industry leading [90-day return policy](http://www.healthwarehouse.com/return-policy) with no restocking fees and only sell products which are FDA approved and legal in the United States. We consistently achieve [high scores in customer satisfaction](http://www.healthwarehouse.com/reviews) and offer some of the best prices on the Internet. We're committed to 100% customer satisfaction. If for any reason, you are dissatisfied with your purchase, our service, or even our website, we will do everything possible to make it right. This is our commitment to you.**

## Privacy Policy

Your privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate and disclose and make use of personal information. The following outlines our privacy policy.

  * Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the purposes for which information is being collected. 
  * We will collect and use of personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other compatible purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law. 
  * We will only retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes. 
  * We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned. 
  * Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete, and up-to-date. 
  * We will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification. 
  * We will make readily available to customers information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information. 

We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained.
